

export const data  = [
  {
    questionId: 1,
    question: "Which of the following statement is correct?",
    option1: "js is Server Side Language.",
    option2: "js is the Client Side Language.",
    option3: "js is both Server Side and Client Side Language.",
    option4: "None of the above.",
    answerText: "js is Server Side Language.",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    questionId: 2,
    question: "What does the REPL stand for?",
    option1: "REPL stands for 'Read Eval Print Loop.'",
    option2: "REPL stands for 'Research Eval Program Learn.'",
    option3: "REPL stands for 'Read Earn Point Learn'.",
    option4: "REPL stands for 'Read Eval Point Loop'.",
    answerText: "REPL stands for 'Read Eval Print Loop.'",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    questionId: 3,
    question: " The Node.js modules can be exposed using:",
    option1: "expose",
    option2: "module",
    option3: "exports",
    option4: "All of the above",
    answerText: "exports",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    questionId: 4,
    question: "In which language is Node.js written?",
    option1: "JavaScript",
    option2: "C",
    option3: "C++",
    option4: "All of the above",
    answerText: "All of the above",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    questionId: 5,
    question:
      "Which of the following command is used to install the Node.js express module?",
    option1: "$ npm install express",
    option2: "$ node install express",
    option3: "$ install express",
    option4: "None of the above",
    answerText: "$ npm install express",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    questionId: 6,

    question: "What is Callback?",
      option1: "The callback is a technique in which a method calls back the caller method.",
      option2: "The callback is an asynchronous equivalent for a function.",
      option3: "Both of the above.",
      option4: "None of the above.",
    answerText: "The callback is an asynchronous equivalent for a function.",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    questionId: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is not a benefit of using modules in Express?",
      option1: "It provides a means of dividing up tasks.",
      option2: "It provides a means of reuse of program code.",
      option3: "It provides a means of reducing the size of the program.",
      option4: "It provides a means of testing individual parts of the program.",
    answerText: "It provides a means of reducing the size of the program.",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    questionId: 8,
    question: " What is the default scope in the Node.js application?",
    option1: "Global", 
    option2: "Local", 
    option3: "Global Function", 
    option4: "Local to object",
    answerText: "Local",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    questionId: 9,
    question: "Which of the following engine Node in core?",
    option1:"Chrome V8", 
    option2: "Microsoft Chakra", 
    option3: "SpiderMonkey", 
    option4: "Node En",
    answerText: "Chrome V8",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    questionId: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is not a valid language for Node.js?",
    option1: "JavaScript", 
    option2: "Java", 
    option3: "C", 
    option4: "C++",
    answerText: "Java",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    questionId: 11,
    question:
      "Which of the following types of applications can be built using Node.js?",

      option1: "Web Application",
      option2: "Chat Application",
      option3: "RESTful Service",
      option4: "All of the above",

    answerText: "All of the above",
    answer: 4
  },
];
